1parkplace.com 2018-06-17

# Privacy Policy

Our  pledge to you is simple-we will _**not**_ release any personally identifiable information such as your name, address, e-mail address, phone number, or any other sensitive information without your consent. Please read the following for more in depth information about our privacy policy:

**NOTICE:[Click here](http://www.ftc.gov/) for important information from the Federal Trade Commission about safe surfing.**

**1parkplace, Inc. _Privacy Principles_ :**

To make this privacy policy easy to understand, we have built it around 5 simple privacy principles. ****

**Principle 1:**

We will explicitly ask you when we need information that personally identifies you or allows us to contact you. (“Personal Information”) Generally, Personal information is requested when you register for a newsletter, when you request a particular service/information from us or one of our clients, when you fill out a survey, or when you request additional information. When possible, we will give you a chance to make sure that your personal information is correct and up to date.

**Principle 2:**

We have important business relationships with certain, third party, service partners. Service partners allow us to offer you a broader array of services than we could provide to you on our own and assist us in the operation of our site. Our preferred service partners, and 1parkplace, utilize personal information only to provide on-going service and support for our client’s websites and other related services. Additionally, 1parkplace will bring you updated or new features, products and services, that become available to you as a valued 1parkplace member.

**Principle 3:**

We do not believe that any portion of our site or services directly solicits children 13 years old or younger. However, if we develop a portion of our site or services that does directly solicit children age 13 years old or younger, we will not directly solicit personal information from children. We will also not provide it for other company’s use without first obtaining the consent of a parent or guardian. If possible, we will also endeavor to provide e-mail notice to parents that their children have provided personal information to the site.

**Principle 4:**

We may disclose personal information, if required, to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with the legal process served on us or our affiliates; (b) protect and defend our rights or property of those or our users, and (c) act as immediately necessary in order to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.

**Principle 5:**

If at any time you believe that we have violated these policies, please notify us by e-mail at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) and we will use all commercially reasonable efforts to promptly investigate and remedy the problem.
